Preliminary Guide to the James Tobin Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, Accession 2005-M-006
  - Yale University. Local 34 strike in 1984
    - Letter from Tobin to Roger Tobin and Linda Blum describing the strike, [1984] (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Reports, memoranda, and newsletters, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 4)
- Additional Material, 1963-1987; Accession 2006-M-100
  This accession consists of materials contributed to the collection by William C. Brainard.
  - Student loans and tuition postponement programs, 1968-1987, undated (Box 1)
  - Ford Foundation, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, and Yale University study on future United States economic growth, 1963-1967, undated (Box 1)
  - McGovern, George, campaign, 1967-1972, undated (Box 2)
  - University endowments, 1970-1978, undated (Box 2)
- Additional Material, 1993-1996; Accession 2006-M-101
  Original audio, film, and video recordings, as well as preservation masters and duplicating masters may not be played. Readers may only play use copies. If a use copy of a particular recording does not exist, researchers must consult with the reference archivist for policies and procedures regarding the creation of duplicating master and use copies of original recordings.
  - Interview with Tobin, 1996 November 7 (Box 1)
  - XIX International Conference, "The Third Round: The Sunshine Economy" [on Mediterranean tourism; organized by the Pio Manzù Research Centre, 1993 October (Box 2)
- Additional Material, 1947; Accession 2007-M-009
  - "A Theoretical and Statistical Analysis of Consumer Saving," [James Tobin's Harvard Ph.D. dissertation], 1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)